Volatility is a very general metric of variability in returns,
波动率是很基本的收益率变化指标
so it's used in many ways.
有很多种用途
In this video, we're going to mention a few possible ways that might be used in trading,
在本视频中 我们将介绍波动率在交易中的几种用法
but there are many more possibilities.
但还有很多其他用法
First, you can classify stocks as highly volatile or less volatile.
首先 你可以将股票分类为高度波动或不太波动
Some strategies might work best on low volatility stocks,
某些策略最适合低波动率股票
so you could use the volatility metric to limit your universe.
你可以使用波动率指标限制股票池
For example, one type of strategy called a mean reverting strategy is to take
例如 有一种策略叫做均值回归策略
a short position on an asset when it
当资产升值时 它会做空股票
appreciates because you think it will depreciate again.
因为你认为该资产将再次贬值
If a stock has low volatility,
如果股票的波动率低
you may think there is less uncertainty in its fair value.
你可能认为它的公允价值不确定性更少
So, after a large deviation from its fair value,
所以偏离公允价值很大时
its price is more likely to revert.
它的价格更有可能回归
Another interesting observation about low volatility stocks is
低波动率股票还有一个有趣的特性
that they actually seem to perform well compared to high volatility stocks.
与高波动率股票相比 它们似乎业绩不错
In finance in general,
在金融领域
greater risk is thought to accompany greater returns.
我们认为更高的风险伴随着更高的收益
So, the empirical observation that
所以经验发现低波动率股票
low volatility stocks outperform high-volatility stocks is considered a mystery.
比高波动率股票业绩更好一直是一个谜
One explanation is that people ignore really boring things in favor of exciting stocks,
一种解释是人们会忽略非常无聊的事物 喜欢令人兴奋的股票
like the tortoise and the hare.
就像龟兔赛跑
The low volatility tortoise is chugging along,
低波动率的乌龟一直在坚持
but people are buying the high-volatility hare stocks.
但是人们喜欢购买高波动率的“兔子”股票
Some exchange traded funds specifically optimized for
有些交易所交易基金专门针对低波动率进行优化
low volatility and seek to include low volatility stocks.
并包含低波动率股票
We'll talk more about exchange traded funds in future lessons.
我们将在后续课程中详细讲解交易所交易基金
Another way to use volatility is to normalize another metric.
波动率的另一个用途是正态化其他指标
Let me explain what I mean by that.
我来解释下
Say you have a momentum signal consisting of returns over the previous year,
假设你有一个动量信号 由上一年的收益率组成
say both Netflix and Walmart have a return of 30%.
假设 Netflix 和 Walmart 的收益率都是 30%
This may seem to mean they're doing equally well,
似乎它们表现一样
but in fact, Netflix is much more volatile,
但实际上 Netflix 波动率高多了
it can move 30% in a week.
它一周就变化 30%
So, you could normalize your momentum signal by dividing by the volatility.
你可以通过除以波动率来正态化动量信号
The idea is to make the comparison apples to apples.
原理是比较同等事物
This theme exists all over the place.
这种原理到处都有应用
If you want to compare any signal across your entire universe,
如果你想比较整个股票池中的任何信号
you usually get some benefit by standardizing it in this way.
通常标准化会比较有用
You can also use volatility to help you determine position sizes.
还可以使用波动率判断头寸大小
In general, quant traders utilize smaller position sizes in
通常 当市场比较波动时
their strategies when markets are volatile to minimize the volatility of net profits,
量化交易者会利用更小的头寸大小来尽量减小净利润的波动率
commonly called profit and loss, or P&amp;L.
净利润通常称为损益 (P&amp;L)
Moreover, the volatility of overall portfolio, P&amp;L,
此外 总体投资组合的波动率 P&amp;L
is often used as a gauge of the professional ability of
经常用于衡量投资组合经理
portfolio managers managing multiple trading strategies.
管理多个交易策略的专业能力
So, the ability to allocate capital,
所以能够分配资本
taking volatility into account becomes very important.
并考虑波动率很重要
If you believe you can forecast volatility with a certain level of confidence,
如果你认为你能以某个置信水平预测波动率
you can adjust your portfolio sizing in anticipation of a pending storm in the market.
那么你可以根据预测的市场风暴调整投资组合规模
But how would you decide how much money to move?
但是如何决定要投入多少金额？
Well, you can include volatility in
你可以把波动率加入到
a formula used to determine the size of your positions.
确定头寸大小的公式中
Every trader might do this slightly differently,
不同交易者的做法可能有所不同
but as an example,
举个例子
a trader might use a formula like this.
交易者可能会使用这样的公式
R divided by sigma times M times last close equals position size,
R/(σ*M*LastClose) =  PositionSize
where r is the dollar amount the trader is willing to lose if
R 表示当 M 倍 sigma 的损失事件发生时
an M sigma event occurs against her or his position.
交易者愿意损失的金额数量
Sigma is the annualized volatility of the security or strategy in question,
σ 是相应证券或策略的年化波动率
M is a trader to find integer,
M 是交易者定义的整数
last close is the last closing price of
LastClose 是证券的上个收盘价
the security or the equivalent for a portfolio of stocks,
或投资组合整体的价格
and position size is the number of stocks to trade.
PositionSize 是要交易的股票数量
This will lead to smaller position sizes for more expensive and more volatile assets.
根据此公式 资产价格越昂贵 波动率越大 头寸越小
If you determine your position using a formula like this,
如果你根据此公式确定头寸
then when you notice market conditions changing,
那么当你发现市场条件变化时
you might decide to recalculate and adjust your position sizes accordingly.
你可能会重新计算并相应地调整头寸大小
Sometimes trading strategies define thresholds at which to
有时候 交易策略会定义一个阈值
automatically sell a stock to take a guaranteed profit or limit losses.
达到此阈值就会自动卖出股票 确保能获利或降低损失
An upper threshold is called the take profit level,
上限称为获利平仓点
while a lower threshold is called a stop-loss level.
下限称为止损平仓点
These might be defined as a target price or as a percent change from an entry price.
它们可以定义为目标价格或买入价的百分比变化
However, if market volatility increases,
但是 如果市场波动率上升了
many stocks might reach these levels more frequently causing more frequent trades.
很多股票可能会更频繁地达到这些水平 导致交易更频繁
During volatile times, traders might adjust these thresholds accordingly.
在波动时期 交易者可能会相应地调整这些阈值